#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jessica-florencia-a4443b82 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Mathematics

**Sports** 

Video Games

## Languages

Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)

# Jessica Florencia

Quality and Policy Lead at Accenture Kuala Lumpur

## Summary

Experienced Co-Founder with a demonstrated history of working in the leisure, travel & tourism industry. Skilled in Quality Auditing, Data Analysis, Microsoft Office, Mathematics, and Research. Strong business development professional with a Bachelor of Arts (BA) focused in Chinese Language and Literature from South China Normal University. Working at Accenture Operations for 4 years, Policy Process Lead for past 2 year and now as Quality and Policy Lead

## Experience

Accenture

4 years 5 months

Quality and Policy Lead

April 2021 - Present (9 months)

Kuala Lumpur, Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Overall Quality and Policy Lead for 12 Operation Project. Responsible for providing Quality insight, feedback and suggestion. Knowledge in RCA report (Root Cause Analyst), Performance coaching. Provide policy opportunities and improvement to client. Propose new automation and create Value to clients and customers

**Quality Team Lead** 

October 2019 - April 2021 (1 year 7 months)

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Policy Team Lead

November 2018 - October 2019 (1 year)

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Policy Team Lead - Chinese, Japanese, Korean, Burmese, Vietnamese, Malaysia Markets

Policy Analyst

August 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 4 months)

Kuala Lumpur

#### Policy Analyst for APEC religion

**Galaxy Lines** 

Co Founder

November 2015 - Present (6 years 2 months)

Establish: 1 November 2015

**ITBS Business Solutions** 

Data Analyst

June 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 3 months)

Kuala Lumpur, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Content Reviewer

Guangzhou Meyo StemCell Hospital

**Assistant Doctor** 

June 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Indonesia Kuala Lumpur

Work overseas

PT Gayo Lues Tamoratama

Translator

September 2013 - March 2014 (7 months)

## Education

South China Normal University

Bachelor of Arts (BA), Chinese Language and Literature · (2009 - 2013)

Sutomo 1

· (2006 - 2009)